Hello.  Vikas Verma ji is with me again today.
Hello Vikas Verma ji.
Hello sir.
Yes.  Vikas Verma ji is the husband of Tamanna Verma ji,
who had a truck which was burnt.
The whole thing got burnt and the insurance company
said that they will not give you 100% claim of IDB.
Will give 75%.  Otherwise your claim will be declared as no
claim.  And they actually made that
claim a no claim.  What did you say when you
made no claim?  That it is a mechanical failure.
So brother, if the car catches fire then there is
no question of mechanical failure.  And
every claim due to fire is payable.  Whether something
catches fire in any way, whether it is due to self-ignition or
any other way.  It is not that no
one from the insurance company
knows about this.  Subhash Singh is
from Delhi, he has a friend named Vipin Tyagi.  One
Avtar Singh who is the North India Head and
Sanjeev Mantri who is its MD and CO, do
they not know that the claim for fire
is payable.  I know but don't want to make a claim.
And do you know what the biggest thing is in this
?  First they have written that we will
give you the claim.  And if you take 75% or 80% claim, then
give its acceptance and we will give the claim.
If you ask for 100%, I will no clip it.
Meaning, this happened to him with such bullying.
We played the video of it.  Now
Vikas Verma ji, you tell me that
after the video that we played, I had
suggested you to write to their grievance cell.
So you wrote to Grievance Cell?  Yes,
I had sent an email to their grievance cell
and after sending the email to their grievance cell,
I have Jagdeep Singh Gaur ji.  I received a
call from him and
he told me on the phone that we are
checking it out and we will do the
entire workout for you and tell you after talking to everyone,
but he did not give me
any responsible answer after doing the workout.  Have
n't given it till date.  I am still
asking them to give me the final surveyor
's report.  He has not
given that till date.  I am asking for mail but they are not giving anything on mail.
She agreed to this much that
yes, we have made a small mistake but we will
check it.  Will do workout.   I will
reply to you after working out.
But they completely refused saying that
we
cannot make any claim now.  I am telling them to give
me the final survey report, even the person
who conducted the final survey is
not giving it till now.  There is no one there to
talk to us in a responsible manner.
You wrote an email to Sanjeev Mantri who is its MD
CEO,
I also sent an email to Sanjeev Mantri
who is MD and CEO and after that I
also sent an email to IRDAIA people but
I did not get any response from them either,
till date I have not received any response to my email, so
what do you think that ICIC
Insurance Company, what has it done to you, it is
cheating on me, it is harassing my family.
Absolutely.  I
know how I am living with my family at
this time, facing harassment.  My
wife has been tortured so much.  Her
health also deteriorated so much that she was admitted to the hospital.
And even after that I have
told them that because of your attitude
my family has been so disturbed
that if something happens tomorrow, if something happens,
you people will be responsible.  This is Sanjeev
Minister ji, Avtar Singh ji and this
Subhash Singh ji, these people have
planned to completely finish me off.  They are threatening that we will
not give you the mail at all.
You will not get your claim under any circumstances because
you denied me 75% at that time when I
asked for it.  Now
we are doing the denaai.  We will not give.  And if you
ask them for any answer, there
is a negative response.  The threat is received in full.  It is
available from everywhere.  And no matter how much you check about
ICICI,
you will get the response from the entire public
that their method of giving claims is wrong.   He does
n't give it at all.   Do
you think that Sanjeev Mantri
, Subhash Singh, Avtar
Singh, Gurdeep Kaur, these people do
not know that the claim is payable.  These people
know everything, the claim is payable.  But everyone is busy
saving their jobs
and everyone is busy with their own work.
No one sees that
something is going wrong in someone's family
or his family gets spoiled or
someone in his family gets harassed
or someone reaches such a mental stage, then
what will the person do?
Sanjeev Mantri is the MD of ICICI Lab General
Insurance Company.  He
is the owner.  You wrote an email to him.  I have
sent an email to them as well and when I
spoke to Jagdeep Kaur ji of the Grievance Cell,
I also asked for her number so that it could be shared with me. Neither has
Sanjeev Mantri
ji replied to my email till date
nor have they given me any
contact number. Neither is there any conversation with them nor is
anything happening. On the contrary, you do not even
pick up my phone. After this,
what are you planning to do now?
I have sent a legal notice to Sanjeev Mantri ji but I have
not received any response from him. Till now, I have not received any response and
I do not even think that I will receive any response from him.
So what will you do after this?
Now after this the case will be filed
inside the court and the case will be filed in the court.  But
during this time, if anything untoward happens to my family, to
my children, to my
family, or to my wife, then
Sanjeev Mantri, MD
Avtar Singh, Subhash ji, all of them will be responsible for everything
and I want to tell the Commissioner of Police
that if anything untoward happens to anyone in my family
or anything happens, then for that,
warrants should be issued to immediately arrest Sanjeev Mantri ji, who is MD of ICICI Lobbard, Avtar Singh ji, our Subhash Singh ji and our Vipin Tyagi ji, in case of any untoward incident in my house.
What message do you want to give to the common consumer
?
I want to say that the ICICI Long Bird
company should be completely banned
and the entire
India should come together to protest against it so that the
incident that is happening to me today, the
incident that is happening to my family, does
not happen to anyone else.  No one should even ask about this company
and it should be driven out
of India.
Now as of today, the government has allowed 100% FDI.
What do you want to say about that?
Sir, for this I would like to say that the
government should first think whether the
general public will be harassed by this.  There will be
no harm to the general public.
What conclusions do you draw from your case
?
Sir, I have other vehicles too, with which I
manage my household expenses etc.
But if I had only one car
which has been burnt to ashes and these people
also made this promise to me that you should
give the money to the financier.  We will
give you the full claim.  I also gave the money to the financier.
I am on the verge of committing suicide.
I have taken money from people on interest and
given it to the financier.  I am
paying interest there.  These people are not making my life any better.
Now he raised his hands.
Meaning their aim was to get the money for the financier.
I want to tell the public to pay
attention to what kind of
fraud company ICICI LB General Insurance
Company is. I have many more cases
of ICICI LB General Insurance Company where
they have committed fraud and in many places they do
not even give claims in death cases.
I also had a case where the wife
died and no claim was made.
Saying that we went to his house and he was
sitting and laughing with a woman, hence we will
not give the claim.
Now brother, the person whose wife dies can never
sit and laugh with any woman in his life.  I
mean, who does all this at such points
?  They
employ investigators about which
I have already shared a video earlier.
Which have no base at all.  On the basis of such
creatures who do not have any legal identity, they have made a
no claim on their claim only after appointing an investigator and
he is saying that this is a mechanical failure.
Tell that illiterate person who has nothing to do with claims,
who doesn't know that when a fire breaks out, it's a
fire, he's not a failure.
So this is how ICICI LB company is doing a fraud
with them.  So we have tried that
through this consumer TV channel, we are
making these videos to make the public aware about the kind of harassment that is happening on the
part of ICICI LB General Insurance Company.
So you need to be a little cautious.
Like I had given you the previous video in
which I had told you about the investigator
that you should not entertain him.
Entertaining him is
not in the consumer's favor.  Goes against the consumer.
Where you entertain the insurance surveyor
or entertain the insurance company
directly.
IRDA has issued a circular for consumers and it has
exactly written in it that
which documents you have to give after your loss
and whether you have to give them
to the insurance company or to the surveyor.
You do not have to give any document to anyone.  And
whoever comes to survey or inspect your vehicle,
first
ask for his ID and if he does not show the ID then
assume that he has come to steal from you.  Just
treat him like you would treat a thief.
His case is absolutely genuine.
Their claim is absolutely payable.  The whole
world knows that it is payable.
Even I have spoken to Avtar Singh and he
said that the claim is payable.  And but don't give.
Now I don't know why they are not giving it, if they had
taken 75% then we would have given it.
Meaning, what kind of policy condition do they have in
which 75% of the claim is payable.
Not 100% payable.
So such fraud is happening.  Please Consumer
Protection Authority IRDAI should
come forward and give them justice.  Such a
prayer